Speaker 1: - We appreciate you coming on. I was just talking about your Senate race there. How are things going? I know you had a debate with Ruben Gallego earlier, or last week, I guess, or Sunday, starting the week
Speaker 2: off. How did things go? It looked like from what I saw, he didn't really have much. You kind of cleaned his clock
a
Speaker 3: bit. - Well, that's the consensus, you know. He
Speaker 4: doesn't have much. He's got his record and his record is absolutely dismal. And so he's got to deal with what he's done for the past 10 years,
which is,
Speaker 4: Myra's in more debt, which is tear open at one secure border. He's actually pushed for hits to Social Security and Medicare as well. So he's really hit against every single member in Arizona and our streets are not safe. His homeless population in his district is the fastest growing homeless population in
Speaker 4: in the country so he had that horrible record that he had to try to defend and there is no defending it so he tried to lie and not to mention his horrible treatment of women in his past his family connections to mexican drug cartels i mean this guy's a real disaster and i had to let the people of arizona know about it so we did really well and we're out campaigning hard early voting has started john and people are already getting out there to vote
And
Speaker 4: I feel really good about where we are. Our internal polling
Speaker 5: has showed me leading him by a hair. And I think that's important as we go into this.
And
Speaker 1: you've got former President Trump. He's going to be there today. Do you think that he'll help in the campaign boost here today? Will you see him today? Will you be there in Prescott Valley? Absolutely.
Speaker 6: Absolutely. I'm going to be seeing him in just a few hours.
We
Speaker 5: are so excited. I'm here in Prescott Valley right now.
And
Speaker 5: we're waiting for the president to arrive here in Arizona. Arizona loves President Trump, and
Speaker 7: it's always a big boost to everyone's campaign when he comes and gives us a business. So we're looking forward.
And the
Speaker 8: other thing with Congressman Gallego, so just to be clear for all of our viewers that
Speaker 1: aren't following this race as closely, he's a member of Congress right now. He's running for Senate, but he's voted on a lot of these left-wing agenda. I want you to walk me through some of the things that he has supported while he's been in Congress.
Well, he
Speaker 9: called the border wall, stupid, dumb border wall and said he would never, ever, ever fund it. And now he's trying to
Speaker 10: act like he likes the border wall, which is what I call the extreme makeover of Ruben Gallego. He's voted for biological men
Speaker 5: participating in sports with our girls, which means our daughters and sisters will have to change clothes and shower in front of men.
Speaker 4: And people aren't for that.
Speaker 4: He's actually was the co-sponsor of the George Floyd legislation, which would have defunded the police nationwide and got rid of qualified
Speaker 11: immunity, which would have made our streets even more unsafe than they already are. Defunding the police. I'm sorry, if you're for defunding the police, you shouldn't even be running for
Speaker 4: office. That's the most ridiculous thing I've ever heard. And you can just go back to that progressive caucus in the House of Representatives where all of the bad ideas come from.
Speaker 4: The ideas that make us wonder what in the world's going on. And he was the leader of the Progressive Caucus, who's voted with Kamala Harris and Joe Biden 100 percent of the time, even more than AOC and the squad. He's further to the left than Bernie. He's further to the left than, you know, you name it, any crazy president.
of
Speaker 4: eric swalwell all those folks
Speaker 11: and so he's the one who pushed by the way for fema to spend a billion dollars over the last two years on the illegals that are pouring in and that's why the coffers are empty right now and we can't afford to help americans in need every bad idea he's got his fingerprints on and i
Speaker 1: think trump he's really hit the message of the border in arizona this is what
Speaker 12: he had to say he calls it operation aurora he brought this up over the last few days i'm to play that sound bite and get your
reaction to it.
I
Speaker 13: will invoke the Alien Enemies Act of 1798 to target and dismantle every
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): migrant criminal network operating on American soil. And we will call it Operation Aurora. That's what we're going to in honor of the people that have suffered in Aurora. But if they come back
into
Speaker 15: our country it's an automatic 10 years in jail with no possibility of parole and i'm hereby calling for the death
Speaker 16: penalty for any migrant that kills an american citizen or law enforcement officer do you think
that foreign
Speaker 17: person trouble had that message again in arizona today uh when he's when he attends this rally
- I
Speaker 10: believe he will. I mean, we are suffering just as bad as Colorado. We have the Trend Aragua gang that is here in Arizona. We have Chilean gangs
Speaker 11: that are robbing people. They're called the dinnertime bandits. They're breaking into people's homes and robbing all of their valuables at dinnertime. This has been happening for the last three and a
Speaker 4: half years. And my opponent is never gonna vote for that. He's never gonna approve of that because he's, like I said, family ties to the cartels, a convicted felon,
Speaker 4: close family member, his father, a convicted felon who was a drug trafficker for the cartels. This is somebody who's not going to get serious and come after the cartels. And as you heard there, President Trump wants to take on the cartels, take on the criminals who are pouring across our border. My opponent said he never wants
Speaker 11: to make anybody leave
our
Speaker 11: to leave our country to come in illegally. Now he's changing his tune, but I want to see everybody who's poured in during the Biden
Speaker 19: invasion sent back to their homeland. We need to repatriate these people back to their homeland so that we can save our homeland. Absolutely
Speaker 17: correct. And, you know, we heard that messaging, Operation Aurora, I imagine he's going to touch on that again when he's in Arizona today. Republican Senate candidate Carrie Lake, thank you so much for taking time. I will be in Arizona for election
Speaker 20: night. Looking forward to it.
For
Speaker 4: your viewers, go to CarrieLake.com. Chip in and help. $5 or $10 will help us get the ads out that we need to warn people about who my opponent is.
Speaker 21: Carrie Lakes, thank you so much. Best of luck. We'll be following it very
Speaker 11: closely. Thank you.
All right, coming up
Speaker 11: next, we are going to...